Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series X. Faculty and Staff
  - Biographical Files (including photographs)
    - Administrative Personnel
      - Quirk, Howard E. (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Selden, Shenetta (Box 31, Folder 24)
        Student services
      - Semmler, John Charles (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Smith, Robert F. (Box 31, Folder 26)
        Biomedical Communications
      - Sweet, Jai R. (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Trethaway, Edward J. "Ned" (Box 31, Folder 28)
        Development
      - Voiland, Bonita S. (Box 31, Folder 29)
        Assistant dean - public affairs and development; See also Edward J. Trethaway Papers 41-5-2617
      - Webster, Robert James (Box 31, Folder 30)
        Engineer
      - Wheeler, Gene (Box 31, Folder 31)
        Assistant dean - financial affairs
      - Willis, George (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Wilson, Archie (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Library Personnel
      - Burnett, Nellie Marie Reed (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Heyns, Erla P. (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Purrington, Alice (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Reinap, Mia (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Whitaker, Susanne K. (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Williams, Edith Clifford (Box 31, Folder 39-43)
    - Clinical and Technical Personnel
      - Alo, Debbie (Box 31, Folder 44)
        Clinical support
      - Angstrom, Clement I. (Box 31, Folder 45)
        Veterinarian; Poultry diagnostic lab
      - Asmua, Henry (Box 31, Folder 46)
        18??-1939
        Farrier: See also Faculty file
      - Asmus, Henry (Box 31, Folder 47)
        Farrier; See also Faculty file
      - Bartholomew, Patricia (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Bigler, Laura (Box 31, Folder 49)
        Veterinarian; Diagnostic lab
      - Blackedge, George (Box 31, Folder 50)
        Graduate student
      - Caldwell, Katie (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - Conklin, Marshall "Buster" (Box 31, Folder 52)
        1926-2011
        Farrier
      - Craig, Peter H. (Box 31, Folder 53)
        Veterinarian
      - Fairbrother, ? (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - Fielder, H. G. (Box 31, Folder 55)
      - Hoshino, Takata? (Box 31, Folder 56)
        Microbiology
      - Johndrew, O. F., Jr. (Box 31, Folder 57)
      - Joo, Kim (Box 31, Folder 58)
        Physiology
      - Kelly, Diane (Box 31, Folder 59)
      - Koland, ? (Box 31, Folder 60)
      - Kraft, Marie (Box 31, Folder 61)
        Laboratory technician
      - Kramer, Larry (Box 31, Folder 62)
      - Layton, Eugene W. "Gene" (Box 31, Folder 63)
      - Lopes, ? (Box 31, Folder 64)
        Baker Institute
      - Medway, William (Box 31, Folder 65)
      - Monlux, William S. (Box 31, Folder 66)
      - Mowers, Harold (Box 31, Folder 67)
      - Olm, Dale (Box 31, Folder 68)
      - Rich, Lon D (Box 31, Folder 69)
      - Rivkin, Lawrence S. (Box 31, Folder 70)
        Pharmacist
      - Ryan, Gerald (Box 31, Folder 71)
        Radiological technician
      - Schultz, Ronald (Box 31, Folder 72)
      - Shannon, Kevin (Box 31, Folder 73)
      - Weiss, Richard C. (Box 31, Folder 74)
      - Weisman, Ziva M. (Box 31, Folder 75)
        Research associate
      - White, Gershorn Franklin (Box 31, Folder 76)
      - Wildenstein, Michael Jon (Box 31, Folder 77)
      - Williams, Jim (Box 31, Folder 78)
      - Williams, Raymond C. (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Non-Cornell
      - Amand, Wilbur (Box 31, Folder 80)
      - Barber, Clifford W. (Box 31, Folder 81)
      - Benjamine, Maxine (Box 31, Folder 82)
      - Callis, Jerry J. (Box 31, Folder 83)
      - Detweiler, David K. (Box 31, Folder 84)
      - Dunlop, Robert H. (Box 31, Folder 85)
      - Gordon, Ruth (Box 31, Folder 86)
      - Goss, Leonard J. (Box 31, Folder 87)
      - Kennedy, Peter (Box 31, Folder 88)
      - Leathem, James H. (Box 31, Folder 89)
      - Meyer, Hermann (Box 31, Folder 90)
      - Patterson, Fred D. (Box 31, Folder 91)
      - Paine, Loyal C. (Box 31, Folder 92)
      - Pilchard, Edwin Ivan (Box 31, Folder 93)
      - Preuss, Fritz R. (Box 31, Folder 94)
      - Sanjar, M. (Box 31, Folder 95)
      - Saunders, Leon Z. (Box 31, Folder 96)
      - Twardock, Arthur R. (Box 31, Folder 97)
      - West, R. Leland (Box 31, Folder 98)
      - Wojciechowski, Krzysztof Jan (Box 31, Folder 99)
  - Millennium Video Project Interviews
    - Millennium Video Project - General Planning, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 100)
    - Millennium Video Project - Franklin M. Loew Interview, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 101)
    - Millennium Video Project - Edward C. Melby Jr. Interview, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 102)
    - Millennium Video Project - Robert D. Phemister Interview, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 103)
  - Faculty Portraits
    These photos have been digitized and are available in Shared Shelf.
    - Appel, Max J. G. (Box 32)
      1964 - 1997
    - Baker, James A. (Box 32)
      1947 - 1975
    - Baker, James A. (Box 32)
    - Baker, Donald W. (Box 32)
      1929 - 1965
      Pathology and Bacteriology
    - Bergman, Emmett N. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1989
    - Bloom, Stephen (Box 32)
      1991-2011
      Microbiology and Immunology
    - Blue, Julia Tait (Box 32)
      1980 - 2002
      Population Medicine and Diagnostic Science
    - Boyer, Jr., Clyde I. (Box 32)
      1952 - 1980
      Laboratory Animal Medicine
    - Brunner, Michael A. (Box 32)
      1980 - 1999
    - Burner, Dorsey W. (Box 32)
      "1931 - 1937 1949-1972"
    - Calnek, Bruce W. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1995
      Avian and Aquatic Medicine
    - Campbell, S. Gordon (Box 32)
      1967 - 1997
    - Carmichael, Leland E. (Box 32)
      1956 - 1997
      Clinical Sciences
    - Comar, Cyril L. (Box 32)
      1957 - 1975
      Physical Biology
    - Concannon, Patrick W. (Box 32)
      1972 - 1999
      Biomedical Sciences - Physiology
    - Cooper, Barry J. (Box 32)
      1977 - 2002
      Biomedical Sciences
    - Corradino, Robert A. (Box 32)
      1966 - 1999
    - Cummings, John F. (Box 32)
      1976 - 1996
      Anatomy
    - Danks, A. Gordon (Box 32)
      1936 - 1969
      Large Animal Surgery - Student Administration
    - de Lahunta, Alexander (Box 32)
      1960 - 2005
      Anatomy - Neurology
    - DeNoronha, Fernando (Box 32)
      1968 - 1995
    - Dobson, Alan (Box 32)
    - Dukes, H. Hugh (Box 32)
      1932 - 1960
    - Dye, J. A. (Box 32)
      1940 - 1960
    - Evans, Howard E. (Box 32)
      1950 - 1986
    - Fabricant, Julius (Box 32)
      1946 - 1985
      Avian Diseases
    - Field, Lincoln E. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1971
      Large Animal Medicine, Obstatrics and Surgery
    - Fincher, Myron G. (Box 32)
      1920 - 1965
      Medicine and Obstetrics
    - Fox, Francis H. (Box 32)
      1947 - 1992
      Large Animal Clinic
    - Gasteiger, Edgan L. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1987
    - Geary, Jack C. (Box 32)
      1952 - 1959
      Radiology
    - Georgi, Jay R. (Box 32)
      1953 - 1989
      Parasitology
    - Gillespie, James H. (Box 32)
      1946 - 1986
    - Gilman, H. L. (Box 32)
      1919 - 1962
      Bacteriology and Pathology
    - Guthrie, Richard S. (Box 32)
      1956-1972
      Large Animal Medicine, Obstetrics and Surgery
    - Habel, Robert E. (Box 32)
      1947 - 1978
    - Hall, Charles E. (Box 32)
      1969 - 1988
    - Hansel, William (Box 32)
      1946 - 1989
    - Henion, John D. (Box 32)
      1976 - 2002
    - Hillman, Robert B. (Box 32)
      1964 - 1995
    - Hitchner, Stephen B. (Box 32)
      1966 - 1981
    - Holmes, Dorothy F. (Box 32)
      1964 - 1991
    - Houpt, Katherine A. (Box 32)
      1975 - 2009
    - Houpt, T. Richard (Box 32)
      1971 - 2001
    - Jacobson, Richard H. (Box 32)
      1977 - 2000
    - Johnson, Seth D. (Box 32)
      1929 - 1969
    - Kallfelz, Francis (Box 32)
      1973 - 2008
    - King, John M. (Box 32)
      1968 - 1998
      Pathology
    - Kirk, Robert W. (Box 32)
      1952 - 1985
      Small Animal Medicine
    - Krook, Lennart P. (Box 32)
    - Lee, Kyu M. (Box 32)
      1963 - 1987
    - Leibovitz, Louis (Box 32)
      1963 - 1988
    - Lengemann, Frederick W. (Box 32)
      1958 - 1988
    - Leonard, Ellis P. (Box 32)
      1948 - 1969
      Small Animal Medicine and Surgery
    - Levine, P. Philip (Box 32)
      1934 - 1972
    - Lewis, Robert M. (Box 32)
      1975 - 2000
    - Lowe, John E. (Box 32)
      1959 - 1991
      Diagnostic Laboratory
    - Ludders, John (Box 32)
      1989-2011
    - McEntee, Kenneth (Box 32)
      1947 - 1980
    - McGregor, Douglas (Box 32)
      1976-2010
    - Miller, Malcolm E. (Box 32)
    - Minor, Ronald (Box 32)
      1976 - 2007
    - Naqi, Syed A. (Box 32)
      1987 - 2002
    - Nathanielz, Peter W. (Box 32)
      1982 - 2002
    - Norcross, Neil (Box 32)
      1960 - 1994
    - Olafson, Peter (Box 32)
      1926 - 1965
    - Page, Rodney (Box 32)
      1999-2010
    - Pauli, Bendicht (Box 32)
      1987-2011
      Molecular Medicine
    - Peckham, Malcolm C. (Box 32)
      1950 - 1984
    - Postle, Donald S. (Box 32)
    - Quimby, Fred W. (Box 32)
      1979 - 2001
      Biomedical Sciences - Laboratory Animal Medicine
    - Rebhun, William C. (Box 32)
      1976 - 1999
    - Reimers, Thomas J. (Box 32)
      1978 - 1999
    - Rendano, Jr., Victor T. (Box 32)
    - Riis, Ronald (Box 32)
      1974 - 2007
    - Roberts, Stephen J. (Box 32)
      1942 - 1972
    - Robertshaw, David (Box 32)
      1987-2001
    - Sack, Wolfgang O. (Box 32)
    - Saidla, John E. (Box 32)
      1988 - 2000
    - Schat, Karel (Box 32)
      1978-2011
      Micro and Immun
    - Schryver, Herbert F. (Box 32)
      1966 - 1990
    - Scott, Fredric W. (Box 32)
      1968 - 1996
    - Sellers, Alvin F. (Box 32)
      1960 - 1985
    - Sheffy, Ben E. (Box 32)
      1955 - 1985
    - Shin, Sang Jae (Box 32)
      1973 - 2005
      Bacteriology
    - Short, Charles E. (Box 32)
      1977 - 1999
    - Stephenson, Hadley C. (Box 32)
      1919 - 1953
    - Summers, Brian A. (Box 32)
      1976 - 2006
    - Tapper, Daniel N. (Box 32)
      1961 - 1996
    - Wasserman, Robert H. (Box 32)
      1957 - 1997
    - Whitlock, John H. (Box 32)
      1944 - 1979, 1971-1976
      Parasitology - University Trustee
    - Winter, Alexander J. (Box 32)
      1963 - 1995
    - Wootton, John F. (Box 32)
      1962 - 2003
  - General Faculty photographs
    - Dr. Lowe placing a beef bull on a surgical table to remove an interdigital growth on the animal's foot in Schurman Hall/Veterinary Hospital., 1960s? (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Training and Activities of the Veterinarian tree (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Public Health activities (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Fred Kilborne, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Faculty in front of Bailey Hall, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Faculty: James Law Hall; V.A. Moore and J. Law at bottom, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Small portraits of students (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - 3 rows of faculty outside building, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Faculty - 3 copies, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - First 6 faculty standing in front of Main Building, 1896 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      Item number: APC10236
    - First 6 faculty seated (full view - head to toe) in front of ivy covered wall with signatures, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - First 6 faculty seated (full view - head to toe) in front of ivy covered wall --- no signatures, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Firt 6 faculty seated (head to waist) in front of trees -- with signatures, 1908 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      Item number: 3-184-86
    - First 6 faculty seated (head to waist) in front of trees -- no signatures, 1908 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - First 6 faculty (except James Law empty seat) seated in front of James Law Hall, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      Item number: 230.3
    - First 3 faculty (except James Law, Pierre Fish, Veranus Moore) in front of James Law Hall, June 1934, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      Item number: 230.4
    - Faculty group taken in 1921 under the front portico of James Law Hall, 1921 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      Item number: 200.1921
    - Faculty group taken in spring 1937 in front of portico of James Law Hall -- 2- versions: SH Gage facing forward, no hat on ground; SH Gage looking to right, hat on ground, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      Item number: 200.1937
    - Faculty group taken in 1946 in front of the Medical Clinic Building, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      Item number: 200.1946
    - Faculty group taken in June 1959 in front of Schurman Hall, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      Item number: 200.1959
    - Faculty group taken in 1963 in front on Schurman Hall, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      Item number: 200.1963
    - Faculty group taken in May 1970 in front of Schurman Hall, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      Item number: 200.197O
    - Faculty group taken in 1974 in front of Schurman Hall, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      Item number: 200.1974
    - Centennial faculty in front of Schurman Hall on September 5, 1996, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Two rows of people in whites in front of old Surgery building; Veranus Moore seated front row 4th from right, Undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Faculty meeting in Oct 13 1955 held in conference room in Moore Laboratory Building, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Pathology and Bacteriology Seminar held in the seminar room of Moore Laboratory Building; graduate student WM Monlux speaking, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      Item number: 313
    - Physiology Seminar for AS Parks visit in Law Hall 1955, Undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Anatomy faculty -- Dr Malcolm Miller, Dr Howard Evans, Dr Robert Habel -- at AVMA 92nd meeting entrance, Minneapolis, August 1955, Undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Editors of the Cornell Veterinarian - DH Udall, D Murphy, CG Rickard, PP Levine -- 2 versions, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      Item number: 210.1949
    - Three rows of men in front of Schurman Hall (Drs Peter Olafson (6th from left; Gorden Danks, 8th from left), Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - 4 men - LS Corwin, SJ Roberts, Joe Engle, Pat Noonan, Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - 6 men - Joe Thomas, Leo McConnell, Donald W Baker, Seth Johnson, Lew Woodworth, Harry Temple, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Faculty on ship on ocean; Dean William Hagan on right, Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
      Item number: 210.1953
    - 4 men in front of stone building; Dr. Myron Fincher (2nd from left), Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - 6 men standing in line: Dr. Francis Fox (3rd from right); Dr. Myron Fincher (2nd from right), Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - 10 men some in white blazer jackets in front of blinded windows; Includes Dr. Hadley Stephenson and Dr. Myron Fincher, Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Dr. John Saidla (left) and Dr. Susan Hackett (right)holding a large framed veterinary insignia plaque, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Dr. Donald Delahanty??, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Dr. Melisa Woan, Research Associate, Baker Institute, looking at microscope, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
      Item number: 1985
    - Dr. Melisa Woan, Research Associate, Baker Institute, at microscope looking forward, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Dr. Gary Cockerell (right in stripped shirt), Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Dr. Robert W. Lewis (left holding cup), Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Samuel Brunett sitting in a chair, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
      Item number: 3-160-86
    - Alexander deLahunta conversing with Dean Donald F. Smith, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
      Item number: UP 0573-04-#082
    - Hugh H Dukes receiving outstanding service award from Dr. Nicholas H. Booth, president of the American Society of Veterinary Physiologists and Pharmacologists At Colorado State University in August 1960, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Brian R. H. Farrow portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Francis H. Fox portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Robert W. Kirk portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - George Kollias holding a raptor (eagle, hawk, etc), Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Robert M Lewis (chair dept Pathology) with a graduate student?, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Howard Jay Milks, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Richard Rawson portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Ronald Riis portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Stephen J Roberts gives award to Dr Niel W. Pieper 1965, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Stephen J Roberts (right) receives AVMA Judiciary Council award from Dr EE Leasure 1967, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Stephen J Roberts (left) with DVM students on 1937 Intercollegiate Champion Polo Team: Steve Roberts '38, CC Combs '39 and TH Lawrence '38, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - David Robertshaw portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - John Saidla portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - John Saidla holding with Dr. Susan Hackett holding an AVMA award plaque, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Richard Suess portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Hadley Stephenson giving an award to an unidentified man and woman, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Jack Tasker (right), Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Lauren Trepanier portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Denny H. Udall, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Alexander Zeissig April 1964, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Deans and Presidents
    - James Law - as a young man with black beard, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - James Law - Woodcut etching of James Law facing right with a black beard and signature; appeared in Elmira newspaper April 2, 1879 with an article, 1879 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - James Law - Early Cornell faculty oval composite with James Law in upper left, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.8
    - James Law - facing right seated looking down at a magazine; signature " Yours very truly, James Law", Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - James Law - facing right seated looking down at a magazine in hand, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.1
    - James Law - facing right seated looking down with monocle and signature, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.21
    - James Law - facing right with monocle, 1908 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.6
    - James Law - facing right with monocle, 1908 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: POST
    - James Law - seated facing right looking down at a black book in hand, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.2
    - James Law - seated looking full face left holding papers in hand from oil portrait in frame, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.3
    - James Law - seated looking full face to left holding papers in hand, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.41
    - James Law - looking left with white beard in oval, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - James Law - looking left with white beard in oval, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.4 copy 2
    - James Law - facing left - closeup, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - James Law - as older man facing right with white beardand stripped tie in oval [removed from class composite?), Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Item number: 221.5
    - James Law - facing forward - taken from photo of 6 original faculty members, Undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Veranus Moore - color oil portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Veranus Moore- as a young man, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 10-98-93
    - Veranus Moore - facing left - as young man without glasses and signature, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Veranus Moore - facing left with glasses; photo taken by White Studios, New York City; in folded album, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.1
    - Veranus Moore - facing right, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.2
    - Veranus Moore - facing left with glasses in oval, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.3
    - Veranus Moore - facing left with glasses, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.4
    - Veranus Moore - standing facing left in oil portrait frame and signature 1929, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.5
    - Veranus Moore - facing left with glasses, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.6
    - Veranus Moore - facing right with glasses, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: 222.7
    - Veranus Moore - Micrograph images of Trypanosoma evansi - photo taken by [Theobald] Smith and Kingman?, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Item number: micrograph
    - Veranus Moore - Micrograph of bacillus of hog cholera showing flagella x 1000…taken by Dr. Wmlpray, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Veranus Moore - Micrograph of anthrax bacillus, 1899, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Veranus Moore and Pierre Fish with signatures from 1931 class composite 220-1 3-156-86 3-157-86, Undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Item number: 220.1
    - Veranus Moore with signature from 1931 class composite 220-1 3-156-86 3-157-86, Undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Item number: 220.1A
    - Pierre Fish with signature from 1931 class composite 220-1 3-156-86 3-157-86, Undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Item number: 220.1B
    - Pierre A. Fish - facing left straight on with signature, Undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Item number: 223.1
    - Pierre A. Fish - in WWI military uniform - May 25 1922, 1922 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Item number: 223.2
    - Pierre A. Fish - facing left in oil portrait, Undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Item number: 223.4
    - Pierre A. Fish - facing forward with half glasses, Undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Item number: 223.5
    - William A Hagan - facing left, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 224.1
    - William A Hagan - pointing to architect schematic model of the veterinary complex to be built in east campus at the New York State Veterinary Medical Society meeting held in Elmira, NY, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - with Dr. GH Hart and Dr Russel Grieg, Edinburgh, Scotland, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - receiving 1st AVMA Fido Award at the Gaines breakfast in New York City, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - at desk with pen and papers, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - oil portrait in frame, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - standing in front of James Law Hall; photo taken by Andre Moul Ross, class of 1943, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A. Hagan - holding Christmas Letter in hand on his desk with pair of glasses, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 3-185-86
    - William A Hagan - Dr. Earl Sunderville and Dr. Raymond Birch; these three administered the college after the death of Dean Pierre Fish, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 210.193x
    - William A Hagan - group of 4 other persons of unknown importance, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - with Dr. Louis Jullian '00, oldest veterinarian at 47th Annual Conference in 1955, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan - with Mrs Minnie Munderback for student fund, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 8523
    - William A Hagan - with Sir Daniel Cabot and Prof Thomas Dalling, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 1766-A
    - William A Hagan - with Sir Daniel Cabot and Prof Thomas Dalling, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 1766-B
    - William A Hagan - with 3 other people seated, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Item number: 3423-H
    - William A Hagan - SAB Advisory Committee at Ft Detrick, Maryland reviewing autoclave, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - William A Hagan and Dr. George Blackledge at the Research Conference of the Morris Animal Foundation, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - George C Poppensiek - facing left, Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
      Item number: 225.1
    - George C. Poppensiek oil portrait ( black/white), Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)